National Capital Parks (NCP) Photograph Collection P034
Stage
- Parkways
  - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway - Section 2 - Paths, 1937 October 15-1938 January 10 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway - Section 2 - Washout, 1928 August (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway - Section 3 - General Views, 1930 May 21-1938 April 12 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway - Section 3 - High Water, 1928 August 13 00:00:00 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway - Section 3 - Landslide, 1935 April 12 00:00:00 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway - Section 3 - Lyon Mill Bridge, 1930 June 2-1937 February 18 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway - Section 3 - Massachusetts Avenue Culvert, 1931 February 3-1940 February 21 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway - Section 3 - Overpass, 1933 July (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway - Section 3 - P Street Entrance Ramp, 1930 October 20-1937 July 13 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway - Section 3 - Pumping Station, 1928 June 8-1942 April 1 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway - Section 3 - Q Street Bridge Vicinity, 1928 June 8-1936 December 15 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway - Section 3 - Retaining Wall, 1928 June 8-1937 March 19 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway - Section 3 - Road Coping, 1931 September 10-1931 October 12 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway - Section 3 - Waterside Drive Overpass, 1932 June 18-1938 February 1 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway - Section 1 - Pennsylvania Avenue Vicinity (Negative) (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway - Section 1 - Pennsylvania Avenue Vicinity (Negative) (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway - Section 1 - Pennsylvania Avenue Vicinity (Negative) (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway - Section 3 - P Street Entrance Ramp, 1931 February 3 00:00:00 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway - Section 3 - P Street Entrance Ramp, 1931 February 3 00:00:00 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway - Section 1 - Construction (Negative), ca. (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway - Section 1 - Titanic Memorial Vicinity (Negative), 1935 November 26 00:00:00 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway - Section 1 - Titanic Memorial Vicinity (Negative), 1935 November 26 00:00:00 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway - Section 1 - Virginia Avenue Vicinity (Negative), 1935 August 8 00:00:00 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway - Section 2 - Bridges - P Street (Negative) (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway - Section 2 - Bridges - P Street (Negative) (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway - Section 2 - Bridges - P Street (Negative), 1939 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway - Section 2 - P Street Vicinity (Negative), 1940 June (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway - Section 2 - P Street Vicinity (Negative), 1940 June (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway - Section 2 - Bridges - P Street (Negative), 1939 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway - Section 3 - Massachusetts Avenue Culvert (Negative), 1936 November 30 00:00:00 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway - Section 3 - Q Street Bridge Vicinity (Negative), 1936 October 12 00:00:00 (Box 22, Folder 40)
- Presidents of the United States
  - Harding, Warren G., ca. (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Roads
  - Virginia, 1944 May 1-1958 February 15 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Sanitation and Public Health
  - Anacostia River, 1957 September 5 00:00:00 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Canal Road, 1957 April 17 00:00:00 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Chain Bridge, West End, 1952 August 26 00:00:00 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - C & O Canal, 1952 June 10-1957 June 26 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Columbia Island Marina, 1956 October-1957 April (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - East Potomac Park, 1952 July 2 00:00:00 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - George Washington Memorial Parkway, 1952 May 29 00:00:00 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - K Street, 1957 April 30 00:00:00 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Maryland, 1957 May 9 00:00:00 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Potomac River, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Rock Creek Park, 1952 June 3-1957 October 29 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Rosedale Recreation Center, 1952 August 14 00:00:00 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Sycamore Island Canoe Club, 1957 March (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Tidal Basin, 1957 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Virginia - Mount Vernon, 1957 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Virginia - Rosslyn (Worthington Oil Company), 1957 November 21 00:00:00 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Chain Bridge, West End (Negative), 1952 August 26 00:00:00 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Chain Bridge, West End (Negative), 1952 August 26 00:00:00 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Chain Bridge, West End (Negative), 1952 August 26 00:00:00 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Chain Bridge, West End (Negative), 1952 August 26 00:00:00 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - Chain Bridge, West End (Negative), 1952 August 26 00:00:00 (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - Chain Bridge, West End (Negative), 1952 August 26 00:00:00 (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - East Potomac Park (Negative), 1952 July 2 00:00:00 (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - East Potomac Park (Negative), 1952 July 2 00:00:00 (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - East Potomac Park (Negative), 1952 July 2 00:00:00 (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - East Potomac Park (Negative), 1952 July 2 00:00:00 (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - George Washington Memorial Parkway (Negative), 1952 May 29 00:00:00 (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - George Washington Memorial Parkway (Negative), 1952 May 29 00:00:00 (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - George Washington Memorial Parkway (Negative), 1952 May 29 00:00:00 (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - George Washington Memorial Parkway (Negative), 1952 May 29 00:00:00 (Box 22, Folder 54)
  - George Washington Memorial Parkway (Negative), 1952 May 29 00:00:00 (Box 22, Folder 55)
  - Rosedale Recreation Center (Negative), 1952 August 14 00:00:00 (Box 22, Folder 56)
- Sesquicentennial
  - Anacostia Park, 1949 October 28 00:00:00 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Buildings (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - "Salute to Freedom", 1950 April 15 00:00:00 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Stamps, Commemorative, 1950 April 20 00:00:00 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Squares
  - Judiciary Square, 1928 May 2-1939 March 14 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - McPherson Square, 1930 November 24-1938 June (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Sherman Square, 1905 April 17 00:00:00 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - McPherson Square (Negative), 1938 June (Box 22, Folder 57)
  - McPherson Square (Negative), 1938 June (Box 22, Folder 58)
  - McPherson Square (Negative), 1938 June (Box 22, Folder 59)
- Streets
  - 14th Street, NW, 1928 June (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - 15th Street, NW, 1936 November 13 00:00:00 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - 16th Street, NW, 1947-1949 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - 19th Street, NW, 1945 February 23 00:00:00 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - 22nd Street, NW (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - 23rd Street, NW, 1944 March 3 00:00:00 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - K Street, NW, ca. (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - M Street, NW, 1933 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - P Street, NW, 1928 July 20-1945 February 23 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Q Street, NW, 1929 July 2 00:00:00 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Concord Avenue, NW, 1936 May (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Connecticut Avenue. NW, 1947 January 6 00:00:00 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - East Capitol Street, 1929 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Independence Avenue, SW, 1942 February 19-1943 May 28 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Lanier Place, NW, 1946 July 11 00:00:00 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - New Hampshire Avenue, NW, 1944 March 3-1945 February 23 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - New York Avenue, NE, 1936 May (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Ohio Drive, NW, 1949 August 12 00:00:00 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Park Place, NW, 1936 May (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Pennsylvania Avenue, NW, ca. (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Pennsylvania Avenue, SE, 1930 February 6-1931 January 2 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Virginia Avenue, NW (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Pennsylvania Avenue, NW (Negative), 1931 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Pennsylvania Avenue, NW (Negative), 1900 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Pennsylvania Avenue, SE (Negative), 1931 January 2 00:00:00 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Pennsylvania Avenue, SE (Negative), 1931 January 2 00:00:00 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Virginia Avenue, NW (Negative), 1937 August (Box 22, Folder 60)
- Swimming Pools
  - Francis Junior High School, 1928 May 31-1939 August (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - McKinley High School, 1929 May 10-1936 August (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - McKinley High School, 1937 July-1939 August (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Rosedale Recreation Center (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Takoma Recreation Center, 1936 August (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Francis Junior High School (Negative), 1939 August (Box 22, Folder 61)
  - Francis Junior High School (Negative), 1939 August (Box 22, Folder 62)
  - Francis Junior High School (Negative), 1939 August (Box 22, Folder 63)
  - McKinley High School (Negative), 1939 August (Box 22, Folder 64)
  - McKinley High School (Negative), 1939 August (Box 22, Folder 65)
  - McKinley High School (Negative), 1939 August (Box 22, Folder 66)
  - McKinley High School (Negative), 1939 August (Box 22, Folder 67)
  - McKinley High School (Negative) (Box 22, Folder 68)
- Traffic
  - Bridges - 11th Street, SE, 1946 May 23 00:00:00 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Bridges - 14th Street, NW, 1946 May (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Bridges - Arlington Memorial, 1946 May 24-1949 August 24 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Bridges - Benning Road, NE, 1946 May 24 00:00:00 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Bridges - Key Bridge, 1946 May 24 00:00:00 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - East Potomac Park, 1937 November (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Pennsylvania Avenue, SE, 1946 May (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Rock Creek and Potomac Parkway, 1937 November (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Traffic Circles
  - Scott Circle, 1933 May 25-1957 April 24 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Washington Circle, 1931 February 10-1960 June 30 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Scott Circle (Negative), 1941 January 9 00:00:00 (Box 22, Folder 69)
  - Scott Circle (Negative), 1941 January 9 00:00:00 (Box 22, Folder 70)
- WPA
  - Relief Projects, 1936 August 28 00:00:00 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- World War II
  - Bald Eagle Hill - B Battery, 1944 June (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Bridges - Constitution Avenue Temporary, 1944 June 8 00:00:00 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Bridges - M Street, SE, 1944 June (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Bridges - Potomac River Temporary, 1944 June (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Columbia Island, 1944 June 8 00:00:00 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Defenses, 1944 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Haines Point, 1944 June 8 00:00:00 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Miscellaneous Locations, 1944 June (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - National Arboretum - A Battery, 1944 June (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - National Airport, 1944 June (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Parks - Anacostia, 1944 June (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Parks - Rock Creek, 1944 June 8 00:00:00 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Parks - West Potomac, 1944 June 8 00:00:00 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Scrap Metal Drive, 1942 September 18 00:00:00 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Virginia - Falls Church, 1944 June (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Virginia - Fort Scott - C Battery, 1944 June (Box 19, Folder 32)
- Youth
  - Sports, 1947 August 23-1952 September 10 (Box 19, Folder 33)
- C & O Canal
  - Cumberland, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Fireplace - Illegal, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Foxhall Road Government Houses, ca. (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Inspection Trip, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Lockhouses, 1930-1957 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Lockhouses, 1930-1957 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Official Trip, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Official Trip - 2nd Day, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Official Trip - 3rd Day, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Official Trip - Last Day, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Official Trip, 15261 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Official Trip, 15262 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Official Trip, 15264 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Recreation - Barge Trips (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Recreation - Barge Trips, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Recreation - Barge Trips, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Recreation - Barge Trips, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Recreation - Barge Trips, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Recreation - Barge Trips, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Recreation - Barge Trips, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Recreation - Barge Trips, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Recreation - Barge Trips, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Recreation - Barge Trips, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Recreation - Barge Trips, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Recreation - Barge Trips, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Recreation - Barge Trips, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Recreation - Barge Trips, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Recreation - Barge Trips, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Recreation - Barge Trips, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Recreation - Canoe Trips, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Recreation - Canoe Trips, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Recreation - Canoe Trips, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Recreation - Explorer Scouts Post 54, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Recreation - Fishing, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Recreation - Hike of Justice Douglas, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Recreation - Hike of Justice Douglas, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Recreation - Hike of Justice Douglas, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 27)